izismile.com 2019-12-25

# Izismile Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy describes what personal information Izismile (the Site) collects, how Izismile uses this information, how this information may be shared, and what choices and rights you have with respect to this information. Access and use of the Site is subject to this Privacy Policy.

**1\. Collection of Information**

We collect information that you provide us, from third parties, and automatically when you use the Site. We collect information associated with your device using cookies and similar technologies. We may also receive information about your location.

**Information You Provide Us**

We collect information that you provide to us, including your account and profile information, content you submit, your communications, and information you provide to us as part of surveys.

**Account and Profile Information.** When you create an account, we collect information you provide to us, like your name and email address.

**Content you Submit.** We collect information and content that you submit, including your photos, comments and searches.

**Communications.** When you communicate with us (via email, through the Site, or otherwise) we store a copy of your communications.

**Surveys.** If you participate in our surveys we will collect the information you provide to us.

**Automatically Collected Information**

We collect information about your use of the Site, including your IP adress.

**Cookies and Similar Technologies**

We use cookies in connection with your use of the Site to collect information related to what you see and interact with on the Site. Please see our [Cookie Policy](https://izismile.com/cookie_policy.html) for more information on our use of cookies and how to opt-out of cookies.

**2\. Use of Information**

We use the information we collect to provide, support and to communicate with you about the Site. The ways we do this include the following:

a. to provide and improve the Site's functionality; to process, store, and deliver your communications; to provide customer service and support; to respond to your enquiries or requests; to back-up our systems; and to improve the security of the Site;  
b. to display relevant advertising (on the Site and third-party sites) and to evaluate the success of our advertising;  
c. to communicate with you as described in this Privacy Policy;  
d. to comply with our legal obligations; to prosecute or defend a lawsuit, arbitration, or similar legal proceeding; to respond to lawful requests by public authorities (including national security or law enforcement requirements);  
e. to perform research and analysis for our business purposes; and  
f. if you decide to participate, to administer surveys.

Any use of your information that is incompatible with these uses will be disclosed to you in advance so that you may opt out of such uses at your discretion.

**3\. Sharing Your Information**

We do not rent or sell your personal contact information (such as your email address associated with your account registration) to third parties to use for their own marketing purposes. We share information in the following ways:

**Advertisers and Ad Networks**

We use advertising networks and similar companies to serve advertisements on third-party sites and to assist us in evaluating the effectiveness of our advertising. We may work with advertising partners to serve ads on the Site. These types of companies use cookies and similar technologies. We may provide advertising networks, advertising partners, and businesses advertising on the Site with aggregate information but other than hashed information or device identifiers, we do not disclose your name, contact information, or other personal information. For more information, please see our [Cookie Policy](https://izismile.com/cookie_policy.html).

Businesses advertising on the Site may also use cookies or similar technologies to track your activities on the Site. Some of these businesses are participants in the [Network Advertising Initiative](https://izismile.com/go.php?url=https://www.networkadvertising.org/) or the [Digital Advertising Alliance](https://izismile.com/go.php?url=http://digitaladvertisingalliance.org/). Please visit these organisations' opt-out pages to learn about how you may opt out of receiving web-based personalised ads from participating businesses. You can access any settings offered by your mobile operating system to limit ad tracking or install the AppChoices app to learn more about how you may opt out of receiving personalised ads in mobile apps.

[Izismile advertising partners list can be found here](https://izismile.com/izismile_advertising_partners.html).

**Investigations**

We may investigate and disclose information from or about you, as permitted by applicable law, if we believe that such investigation or disclosure is (a) reasonably necessary to comply with legal process and law enforcement instructions and orders, such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, judicial proceeding, or other legal process served on us; (b) helpful to prevent, investigate, or identify possible wrongdoing in connection with the Site; (c) helpful to protect our rights, reputation, property, or that of our visitors, users, corporate affiliates, or the public;or (d) to enforce compliance with our agreements with you.

**4\. Third Party Plug-ins, Widgets, and Links**

the Site may include third-party social media features and other third-party plug-ins and widgets. When these features are displayed on the Site, they are operated or hosted by third parties and are subject to their own privacy policies instead of this Privacy Policy. the Site also contains links to third-party sites that are not controlled or operated by us. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.

**5\. Account Termination**

In order to request permanent closure and deletion of your account, please contact us at admin@izismile.com.

**6\. Children**

The Site is intended for general audiences and is not directed to children under 13. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13, we will take appropriate steps to delete that information. If you become aware or believe that a child has provided us with personal information, please contact us as provided in the Contact Us section.

**7\. Data Security**

We use reasonable and appropriate measures to protect your personal information from loss, misuse, unauthorised access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction, taking into account the risks involved in the processing and the nature of the personal information.

**8\. Updates to this Privacy Policy**

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most current version of our Privacy Policy will govern our use of information about you. If we make material changes to our Privacy Policy, we will notify you by email or by posting a notice on the Site. By continuing to access or use the Site after those changes become effective, you are subject to the revised Privacy Policy.

**9\. Contact Us**

If you have questions or comments about our Privacy Policy,please email us at admin@izismile.com.

**10\. Legal Basis for Processing Personal Information (European Economic Area)**

If you are from the EEA, our legal basis for collecting and using the personal information described in this Privacy Policy will depend on the personal information concerned and the specific context in which we collect it. We collect and use your information for a variety of business purposes that are in our legitimate interests.

If you wish to learn more about specific legal grounds we rely on to process your information for any particular purpose (including any legitimate interests we have to process this information), please contact us as provided under the Contact Us section. For example, we rely on our legitimate interests to process information for direct marketing purposes and for fraud prevention and detection, provided these interests are not overridden by your data protection interests or fundamental rights and freedoms.

**11\. Your Data Protection Rights (European Economic Area)**

In some regions, such as the EEA, you may have certain rights in relation to your personal information, including the right to access, correct, update, or request deletion of your personal information. Izismile takes reasonable steps to ensure that the data we collect is reliable for its intended use, accurate, complete, and up to date. If you have a registered account, you also can manage your profile and settings within the Site. However, if you are not a user of the Site and you want to contact us directly about accessing, correcting, updating, or deleting your personal information, or altering your data or marketing preferences, you can do so at any time by contacting as provided in the Contact Us section. We will consider your request in accordance with applicable laws.

You can object to processing of your personal information, ask us to restrict processing of your personal information, or request portability of your personal information. Again, you can exercise these rights by contacting us as provided in the Contact Us section. You also can deactivate your profile and obtain a copy of your information.

You can complain to a data protection authority about our collection and use of your personal information. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority. Contact details for data protection authorities in the EEA and Switzerland are available [here](https://izismile.com/go.php?url=http://ec.europa.eu/newsroom/article29/item-detail.cfm?item_id=612080).

Similarly, if we have collected and processed your personal information with your consent, then you can withdraw your consent at any time. Withdrawing your consent will not affect the lawfulness of any processing we conducted prior to your withdrawal, nor will it affect processing of your personal information conducted in reliance on lawful processing grounds other than consent.

We respond to all requests we receive from individuals wishing to exercise their data protection rights in accordance with applicable data protection laws. We may ask you to verify your identity in order to help us respond efficiently to your request.

Effective 25th May, 2018
